[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":49024,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":252902,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure th at when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":7345,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":260260,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":6910,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":267179,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1888,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":269076,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":4873,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":273955,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1739,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":275700,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second  one to  it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":8046,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":283752,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1739,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":285502,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":6801,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":292309,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1297,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":293611,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4029,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":297644,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6 </sub> 0  = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1348,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":298996,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":7163,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":306165,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1956,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":308124,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /> <br /> ( Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":5121,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":313247,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":4932,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":318182,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your resu lt.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3764,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":321949,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1353,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":323308,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3601,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":326912,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":5027,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":331943,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3371,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":335316,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1494,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":336813,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":16726,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":353553,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inve rse unde r +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":20594,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":374149,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3983,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":378134,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1895,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":380033,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /> <br /> ( Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":5910,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":385947,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2176,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":388126,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2494,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":390623,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1508,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":392134,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":7197,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":399334,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under  +<sub>6< /sub>.","rt":1597,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":400934,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":12522,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":413458,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1471,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":414932,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed sta rting wi th the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":23534,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":438468,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is  no way t o make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":133290,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":571762,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":32425,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":604198,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1229,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":605432,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a ge nerator  is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":3667,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":609105,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":9996,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":619104,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (R emember,  a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":4213,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":623322,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1322,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":624649,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":5717,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":630369,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1326,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":631698,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understa nd the n ew operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":13150,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":644850,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4","1"],"rt":11638,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":656491,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1390,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":657886,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":4738,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":662627,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3055,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":665686,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4110,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":669803,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2603,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":672412,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3271,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":675690,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":11559,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":687255,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub > 1? Ple ase explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"it adds up to five, which is less than nine, so therefore five is the answer","explanation_history":["it adds up to five, which is less than nine, so therefore five is the answer"],"response_history":["5"],"rt":25083,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":712344,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"it adds up to 12 which is more than nine, so subtract nine and get three as the answer","explanation_history":["it adds up to 12 which is mor eht","it adds up to 12 which is mor eh","it adds up to 12 which is mor e","it adds up to 12 which is mor ","it adds up to 12 which is more than nine,  so subt ract nine and get three as the answer"],"response_history":["3"],"rt":23121,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":735477,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"The identity is still 0 because it's what added to the number gives you the number","explanation_history":["The identity is still 0 because it'w ","The identity is still 0 because it'w","The identity is still 0 because it's what added to the number gives you the number"],"response_history":["The identity is st","0"],"rt":241870,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":977354,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3314,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":980681,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":2495,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":983184,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":6588,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":989776,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Pleas e explai n in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"because if you add 6 to 3 you get nine","explanation_history":["because it twou","because it two","because it tw","because it t","because it ","because it","because it","because if you add 6 to t","because if you add 6 to 3 ye","because if you add 6 to 3 you get nine"],"response_history":["6"],"rt":33594,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1023378,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"because you can't add it to itself several times to get nine","explanation_history":["because you can't add it to itself several times to get nine"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":21332,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1044721,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"yes because you can add it to itself several times to get nine","explanation_history":["yes because you can add it to itself several times to get nine"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":16532,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1061261,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"no because you cannot add it to itself to get nine","explanation_history":["no because you cannot add it to itse lf to ge t nine"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":14887,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1076155,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"no because you cannot add it to itself to get nine","explanation_history":["no because you cannot add it to itself to get nine"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":14426,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1090591,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for  the arb itrary value if necessary.","rt":9846,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1100443,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"n-1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["n-1"],"rt":17444,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1117892,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x-n","explain":true,"explanation":"you want whatever added to n would give you x","explanation_history":["yt","you want wa","you want whatever added to n would give you x"],"response_history":["x-n"],"rt":29405,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1147301,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"look for multiples","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["look for mil","look for mi","look for multiples"],"rt":14800,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1162106,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":6640,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1168750,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":4927,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1173680,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":6260,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1179943,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not  a gener ator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"False","explain":true,"explanation":"well, if it n=9 and x=2, then two is not a generator and it is also not a multiple of a divisor","explanation_history":["well, if it was","well, if it wa","well, if it w","well, if it n=9 and x=2, t","well, if it n=9 and x=2, then two is not a generator and it is also not a mo","well, if it n=9 and x=2, then two is not a generator and it is also not a multiple of a dis","well, if it n=9 and x=2, then two is not a generator and it is also not a multiple of a divos","well, if it n=9 and x=2, then two is not a generator and it is also not a multiple of a divo","well, if it n=9 and x=2, then two is not a generator and it is also not a multiple of a divisor"],"response_history":["False"],"rt":56680,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1236627,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":10516,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1247147,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Never","explain":true,"explanation":"I was wrong, it's never, because that adds up to 0","explanation_history":["I was  wrong, it's never, because that adds up to 0"],"response_history":["Sometimes","Never"],"rt":41416,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1288570,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":20749,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1309333,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1708,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1311045,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age ?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"43","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["43"],"rt":2986,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1314037,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Associates Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Associates Degree"],"rt":3140,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1317182,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is mo st advan ced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Algebra 101 in college and I HATED it...this HIT made my head hurt.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["A","C","Algebre","Algebra 101 in college and I HATED it...this HIT made my head hurt."],"rt":27845,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1345031,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5083,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1350119,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5189,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1355311,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4198,"trial_type":"que stion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1359514,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3467,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1362983,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":4277,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1367264,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"mu lti","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Female"],"rt":2698,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1369969,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":5068,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1375040,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no"],"rt":3597,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1378640,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"my head hurts","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["me","my head hurts"],"rt":19430,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1398073,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]